Guide to the Stanford University, Humanities Honors Program, Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1998-068
  - Moller, Suzanne, The silent struggles: Origins of the Americans with Disability Act of 1990., 1996 (Box 3)
  - Moore, Jane Erin, What is a sentence they mean three: the opaque language of experiment in the work of Gertrude Stein and Georges Perec., May 1996 (Box 3)
  - Nomura, Liane, Student activism in Asian-American studies: providing a link between a classroom and community., 1996 (Box 3)
  - Pan, Arnold L., Music Criticism and the cultural game: an empirical critique of Pierre Bourdieu's cultural theory., Spring 1996 (Box 3)
  - Peterson, Ben, The Malclm X of Rap: A popular study of Hip Hop's disticnt interpretation of Malcolm X. Its evolution and significance., May 1996 (Box 3)
  - Reed, Robert, Aspirations of Afrocentrism., 1995 (Box 4)
  - Sarker, Urmimala, What is Indian? Narrataing Identity in English: Salman Rushdie's Midnight Children and Vikram Seth's A Suitable Boy., May 1995 (Box 4)
  - Schick, Shelley, In Dire Straits: Adolescent Females and Out-of-Home Placement in San Francisco's Juvenile Justice System., 1996 (Box 4)
  - Talbot, Cynthia Haines, Old Nation, New Wisdom: Giambattista Vico's Science of Ancient Humanity., May 1996 (Box 4)
  - Thomas, William, Auobiography, Technologism, and the Possibility of the Self (Vico's Reluctance, Augustin's Example, Foucalt's Tension)., January 1996 (Box 4)
  - Thukral, Renita, Back to the Neighborhoods: A history of the San Jose Unified School District's Twenty-Five Years of Desgregation., undated (Box 4)
  - Williams, Christine L., Formal constraint and narrative devices in Life of a User's Manual by George Perec., May 1996 (Box 4)
  - Yang, Chi-ming, Pseudonymous authorship in Kierkegaard's Either/Or: The anxiety of the aesthetic., June 1996 (Box 4)
  - Ziegler, Robert Todd, Re-examining Werner Heisenberg's philosophical conclusions regarding the structure of matter., April 1996 (Box 4)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1998-285
  - Balli, Cecilia, The public performance of identity in the South Texas Rio Grande Valley., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Black, Lamont, Reformism, Revivalism and the Bhagavadgita: A Look at he Social Movements in the Ninetheenth Century India and the Bhagavadgita's Involvment., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Brennan, Tara, Interracial Interacion and the Harlem Renaissance: Locating Mixed-Race Subjectivity in the Writings of Jean Toomer and Nella Larsen., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Bruch, Mia Sara, Idioms of Intellect: Lionel Trilling and Henry Louis Gates, Jr., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chou, Jennifer Howen, Exploring the relationship between ethnicity and religion: Asian American college students and Christianity., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Curioca, Haydee, Serving the youth body and soul: a history of the Oakland community school., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Drescher, Joel, The politics of righteousness: an examination of the anti-government patriot movement., June 18, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Harmon, Casey, Appreciating Zion: an examination of Wallace Stegner's interest in the Mormon empire of the American West., May 27, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Harms, Julia Christine, Understanding the causes of student-athlete attrition: toward a more comprehensive explanation., Spring 1998 (Box 1)
  - Hoang, Hieu T., Justice, suffering, and truth in Nguyen Du's "The Tale of Kieu" The third trial scene: the power of author's and their limits., June 6, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Houle, Wendy, Superwoman and the gentleman: Gender Ideals in Cosmopolitan and Esquire., May 1998 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Matthew, Fragments from the Jetty., June 1997 (Box 2)
  - Kim, Agnes S., Breakdown of communication: tracing the stunted development of the psyche in James Joyce's Dubliners., August 1997 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Kimberly J., "Who is it that can tell me who i am?": King Lear and the critique of order., Spring 1997 (Box 2)
  - Manuel, Gregory, Lui Shaoqi and Lin Piao Victims of the Anti-Confucial movement., June 1997 (Box 2)
  - Merino, Felipe N., Americn electoral politics: barriers, political representation, and the faith of the Mexican American community., May 27, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Neale, Christopher, Richard Rorty and Jurgen Habermas on the imiportance of Dialogue for Democracy., May 27, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Olsson, Annika, Insuring America' Uninsured children: the crafting and implementation of the 1997 state children's health insurance program., May 1998 (Box 2)
  - Ord, Eleanor M., Orson Welles' Productions of Shakespeare on stage and on screen., May 15, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Park, Won Jung, The problem of the "inner" in Woolfe and Joyce., Spring 1997 (Box 2)
  - Poruri, Laxmi, Chris america: The influence of Chris Ever on playing styles and American tennis culture (Reading the tennis court as a text of American culture)., May 9, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Rosenblum, Joe, Late capitalism and transculturation in Chile: Approaching New Chilean literature at the Turn of the Century., May 15, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Saxon, Eric, Kerouac's quest for spiritual resolution in artistic expression., June 6, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Shin, Laura, Evolving From Religion to Truth: Durkheim and Nietzsche Explain the Irrational.., June 3, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Stein, Teri M., Moments of Seeing: The Language of Cubism in the Novels of Virginia Woolf.., May 23, 1997 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2001-166
  - Agee, Megan, There's No Such Thing as a Free Lunch: The Origins of the National School Lunch Program., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - Auld, Sara, Women and Medicine in the West: Charlotte Blake Brown and the Founding of the San Francisco Children's Hospital, 1875-1904., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - Baribault, Maryann, The American Boycott of the Moscow Olympics: A Study of the Relationship between Politics and Athletics., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - Brubaker, Jared, Different Perspectives on a Shared Identity: The Moriscos of Deza, 1570-1611., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - Carter, Brian Jonas, Doctors of Resistance: A Study of Nineteenth Century Slave Medical Practitioners in the U. S. South., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - Cho, Seung-Min Samuel, The Kwangju Tragedy: An Entanglement of Regionalism and People's Desire for Democracy in the Korean Peninsula., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - DeBakcsy, Dale, Beyond Wagner: The Triumph of Musical Diversity over Nazi Ideology in the Third Reich., May 2001 (Box 1)
  - Goss, Rasanah, Raised to be Slaves: The Childhood Experience During Colonial American Slavery., June 2001 (Box 1)
  - Lau, Olivia Cie, An Explosive Issue in an Era of Social Change: The Evolving Discussion over the Use of he Atomic Bomb in the 1960s., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Marshak, Adam Kolman, The Many Faces of King Herod: Client Kingship and Hellenist Jewish Monarchy in the Herodian Dynasty., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Meyer, Sarah, The Spirit of Enterprise: The Terra Nova Expedition and Captain Scott's Heroic Failure., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Montz, Zachary, The Logic of Escalation: Vietnam Decision-Making in the Johnson Administration., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Mulhauser, Dana, Women at Work: Gender and Class Consciousness in the New York Women's Labor Movement, 1900-1914., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Presser, Elisabeth Catherine, Creation of Authority: John Stuart Mill and the American Civil War., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Rauh, Grace, The May 1968 Student Uprising in Senegal: A Sruggle for Independence., May 2001 (Box 3)
  - Sayn-Wittgenstein, Anna zu, Teaching the History of the Third Reich: Its Affect on German Youth today as Measured and Analyzed 1999-2001., May 2001 (Box 3)
  - Schmidt, Erin, Daughters of Vera: Womanhood in the Early Soviet Era., May 2001 (Box 3)
  - Schwegman, Jeffrey L., The Revolt of Eden: The Transformation of Nature in the Novels of Emile Zola., May 2001 (Box 3)
  - Shamsid-Deen, Masud Shakir, Martin Luther King, Jr. and his Relationship to Africa, 1956-1967., May 2001 (Box 3)
  - Toth, Michael, The Coming of a Capitalist: Religion, Politics, Radicalism and Michael Novak., May 2001 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2002-264
  - Adame, Jaime, The Fence: Grief, Empathy, and Remembrance at the Former Site of the Alfred P. Murrah Building., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Alteveer, Ian, "count counter / I counted"., May 17, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Azim, Dalia, I Shall Have Come Unseen., May 15, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Babcock, Brian, Cyborgs and Nomads: A Vision of Identity for the Information Age., May 15, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Baber, Kristine, New World Representations: Leonora Carrington and the awakened subconscious., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Baca, Michael (Miguel), The Constructed Identities of the Penitente Brotherhood in New Mexico., May 15, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Bass, Margaret, Seeing is Believing: An Examination of the Vogue Body from the 1960s to the 1990s., June 2002 (Box 1)
  - Bernstein-Wax, Jessica, Dostoevsky's Pragmatic Novel: Life Before Logic., 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - Brazeal, Greg, Recovering Transcendence: Pragmatism, Mysticism, Proust., May 15, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Bruncko, Martin, Self, Meaning and Nothingness: Ethical Consequences of Jean-Paul Sartre's Existentialist Conception of Self., May 15, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Chi, Soo-Jean, A Sign of the Times: Jean Luc Godard's A bout de souffle as a Reflection of the Historical, Political, and Social Moment in Late 1950's France., May 15, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Cloyd, Carey, Mourning the Mother in Faulkner's As I Lay Dying., 1999 (Box 2)
  - Cohen, Julia, Majority Staus for "Minority" Students: The Challenges of Desegregation and Realities of Racial Isolation in Redwood City, California., May 2001 (Box 2)
  - Cowan, Katrin M., Story as History: Images of War in American Children's Picture Books., May 24, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Davis, Sara Poggi, Human Ecology in Tournier's Friday., 2001 (Box 2)
  - Dodds, Kady, Franklin Delano Roosevelt's Fireside Chats., May 2002 (Box 2)
  - Franklin, Samira, Minor Narratives: The Displacement of Feminine Stereotypes in the Work of Toni Morrison and Cindy Sherman., May 17, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Hammond, Marian, "How much kissing is to much kissing?": Teenage Pregnancy and Sexuality in Seventeen Magazine, 1954-1981., May 19, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Hanson, Brooke, Reel Charity: Touched by an Angel's Television Spirituality and Promotion of Social Consciousness., June 2002 (Box 3)
  - Holt, Ashley, Reading Comics: Imagining a Reader-Response Theory for a Comic-Book Culture., May 22, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Hopwood, Tara, The Cultivation of the Phenomenon of Performance-Enhancing Drug Use in Sport: the History, with Case Studies in the United States, East Germany and China., Spring 1999 (Box 3)
  - Howell, Benjamin W., Raymond Chandler and the Art of Detective Fiction., May 17, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Hoy, Meredith, The Body in Pixels: Space, Embodiment and Subjectivity in Cinema and Cyber-Culture., Spring 2001 (Box 3)
  - Irons, Julia Rogasner, Narrating Silence, Narrative Silences: The Memoirs of Maxine Hong Kingston and Isabel Allende., May 15, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Kalogeras, Steven M., The U.S. Prison Boom: An Examination of Mass Incarceration in American History., June 10, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Karas, Stan, A Passage to Zembla: The Figure of the Author in Vladimir Nabokov's American Fiction. (Box 4)
  - Karash, Ann, Cecilia Beaux: Representing Femininity., June 4, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Kauffman-Abel, Sarah, The Mystical Critique and the Construction of Authority in Mechthild of Magdeburg's The Flowing Light of the Godhead and Marguerite Porete's the Mirror of Simple Soulw., May 24, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Kim, Agnes S., Breakdown of Communication: Tracing the Stunted Development of the Psyche in James Joyce's Dubliners., August 1997 (Box 4)
  - KIng, Ivory, "How can they call her if they don't know her name?": The Concept of Person in Toni Morrison's Beloved., May 15, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Kinsey, Valerie, After May 1968: Imaging Revolution Through Film--A Study of the Radical Phases of Bernardo Bertolucci & Lina Wertmuller., May 15, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Klein, Jenna, The Role of Harold L. Icles in Advancing Civil Rights for African Americans; Recognizing a New Deal-- Dedicated, Early, Anglo, Leader., May 4, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Lawrence, Matt, Narrating Place and Mapping Mystery: The representaion of urban space and the literary geography of New York City in Abraham's Cahan's Yekl, Steohan Crane's Maggie, and Paul Lawrence Dunbar's The Sport of the Gods., May 2001 (Box 5)
  - Lazar, Lawrence, Aristotle in Love., May 2000 (Box 5)
  - Lee, Sylvia, "Communication is Health; Communication is Happiness": World War I and the Problems of Communication in Virginia Woolf's Jacob's Room and Mrs Dalloway., May 15, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Leytes, Dina, Samuel Beckett: Staging the Life of the Mind., May 2001 (Box 5)
  - Lundstrom, Christopher, The Amerikan Way: Progress and Confinement in Kafka's Amerika., May 1999 (Box 5)
  - Marino, Maura, Balancing Personality and Pedagogy: A Work Plan for Service Learning at East Palo Alto High School., May 2002 (Box 5)
  - Martinez, Simon Esteban, The Critic's Syntax: Rosalind Krauss and the Art magazine, 1966-1976., May 17, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Maruca, Alison, "Anonymity is in their blood": Reviving Judy Chicago's Dinner Party., May 15, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Miner, Luke, Simulated America., September 19, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Narayanan, Kumar, Between Worlds: Guardians of Tibet as Agents of Transformation., May 15, 2000 (Box 6)
  - North, Connie, Perceptions of Womanhood in Late Nineteenth Century Montana: A Comparative Exploration of a Crow and Pioneer Woman's Text., May 1998 (Box 6)
  - Nunley, Jessa, Becoming Freak Unbecoming Female: The Slasher Film, its Finalgirl, and Her Nightmare., May 1999 (Box 6)
  - Pagon, Garrett, Tolstoy and Darwin: The Biology of the Soul., May 15, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Park, Cindy S., The Role of Anti-Semitism in the Oberammergau Passion Play, 1930-2000., May 15, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Pena, Marisa Lynn, Creative Conflict: Dualities of Consciousness, Will, and Time in Three Modern Works The Last Temptation of Christ, Creative Evolution, and The Rainbow by Nikos Kazantzakis, Henri Bergson, and D.H. Lawrence., 1999 (Box 6)
  - Peterson, Megan, "Stop in the Name of Humanity!" Humanity's place in a Technological World as it is Portrayed in Jacques Tati's Mon Oncle and Charles Jones' Roadrunner Cartoons (contains supplemental CD)., May 17, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Price, Zachary, The Totality-Concept and the Critical Standpoint: Young Lukacs on Kierkgard and Dostoevsky., May 15, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Ray, Kimberly M., Time Creative and Destructive in A La Recherche Du Temps Perdu., December, 1997 (Box 6)
  - Saenz, Jessalyn, The Silicon Valley Dream: Popular Renderings and Complicated Realities., June 2, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Sandrik, Sara, Women in Sports Broadcastign: Rapid Progress, Enduring Obstacles., May 23, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Sengupta, Shiladitya, The Phenomenology of Time-Consciousness in Thomas Mann's Doctor Faustas., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Sepiol, J. Alexander, Four Days of Temporary Death: On Jim Carroll's Fall of Grace in The Basketball Diaries., May 17, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Servaites, Jonathan, Authorial and Everyday Aabstraction: Despair in Kierkgard's The Sickness Unto Death., September 1997 (Box 7)
  - Shah, Ankur, What is Subversive About Love?., May 1, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Shoemaker, Daniel, The Terrified Voice: Mythopoesis in Jame Joyce's Finnegan's Wake., 1998 (Box 7)
  - Simpson, Annie, "With Their Teeth Still Set on Edge" The Resilience of Plessy in American Public Education., June 1, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Holiday Rose, American Cowboys and Aryan Warriors., 2000 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Holland, The Cult and Culture of Mikhail Bulgakov's The Master and Margarita., 2001 (Box 7)
  - Sobelle, Geoffrey, The Aesthetics of Postmodernism as Lived Out in a Haunted Space or The Postman's Path through Postwar Bosnia-Hercegovina., 1998 (Box 8)
  - Soman, Nick, "Some Strange Circumstance": White Impacts on the Blues (contains supplemental CD)., May 23, 2002 (Box 8)
  - Stuart-Wolff, Prairie, The Art of Making History: Historical Foundations of Identity and Narrative in the Works of James Joyce and Giambattista Vico., 1999 (Box 8)
  - Thomas, Barbara M., Jusqu'a Zanzibar: Scenes from the Life and Work of Christine Pascal (1953-1996)., Feb. 23, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Thomas, Ryan B., A constellation of chance/Duchamp and Language., May 15, 1998 (Box 8)
  - Tirres, Andrea L., Negotiating Borders: The Case of Operation Hold the Line in El Paso, Texas., June 1999 (Box 8)
  - Travis, Lauren, Living Between the Lines: African American Perceptions of their experience in Japan., 2000-2001 (Box 8)
  - Trop, Gabe, Tarrying with Translation: Language, Aesthetics, and human Emanicipation in Walter Benjamin's "The Task of Translator."., May 15, 1998 (Box 9)
  - Tsang, Matthew W., The Significanace of Obelisks: Monumental Meanings and Interpretations., May 15, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Tung, Michelle, Technology Transformation: The Anime Cyberbabe., 1999 (Box 9)
  - Weisburst, Seth, Confronting the Nightmare of Dresden: history and Deception in Kurt Vonnegut's Mother Night, Cat's Cradle, and Slaughterhouse-Five., May 17, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Weldon, Jon, Liminality, Subversion, and Spectacle in Kerouac's On the Road., 1999 (Box 9)
  - West, Tiffany N., Peter Sellars: Opera for the American Masses., May 1998 (Box 9)
  - Whitehead, Ryan Richard, The Use of Notation: Steve McCaffery's Theory of Sediment and Iannis Xenakis' Formalized Music., May 15, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Young, Kathryne Marie, Trial Technique Manuals as a Source of Legal History: A Look at Expert Witness Cross-Examination in the Twentieth Century., May 15, 2001 (Box 10)
  - Young, Phillip, Cicero and the Officium Bonorum: A Study of Cicero's Letters during the Roman Civil War--49 BC., May 17, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Yun, Jaewon, Selling the Swoosh: The Nike Women's Advertising Campaign., May 21, 1999 (Box 10)
  - Zwarich, Jennifer, From Self-Image to Style: Gendered identities, Sex and Consumerism in Fight Club and Sex and the City., May 2000 (Box 10)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2003-286
  - Buschbacher, Ulkrike, The American Dream: America's Cultural Dictator., May 15, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Davis, Galen, Game Noir: The Construction of Virtual Subjectivity in Computer Gaming., May, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Gordon, Kylie, Body in Motion, Mind at Rest: On Cunningham's "Quieting" Aesthetic., July 11, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Halliday, David, Moral Ambiguity: Cinematography and Visual Literature in Sergio Leone's The Good, The Bad, and the Ugly., 2002 (Box 1)
  - Innes, Erikka, Mary Shelley's Lodore: An Exploration of Feminine Education., May 13, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Lapidus, Micah, Woody Allen and Fyodor Dostoevsky: An Examination of the Ways in Which Woody Allen Consciously Engages Dostoevsky's Crime and Punishment on his Film, Crimes and Misdemeanors., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Lee, Mi, Forging Checks or Consciences?: James Joyce, Wordsmith., December 2001 (Box 1)
  - Matthews, Nathan, Love of the Land., 2002 (Box 1)
  - McNiff, Fiona, New World Fantasy in Ben Jonson's The Alchemist., May 13, 2002 (Box 1)
  - Nguyen, Khai, Imagining Identity: The Search for Self in Doctor Faustus., May 23, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Reinhold, James M., Positively Negative., September 25, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Rosenthal, Lihi, Myth-Makers, Myth-Breakers: Three Women Poets' Reponse to the Female Condition in Israel., Spring, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Shaw-Scott, Ashley, A Look at Jean-Paul Sartre's La Putain Respectueuse: The Play and the Film Adaptation., 2002 (Box 2)
  - Sostek, Katrina, What Characters in Finnegans Wake Could Not Be., Spring 2002 (Box 2)
  - Wrean, Kate Nenneman, The Evolution of Joseph Knecht's Individual Purpose in Hermann Hesse's The Glass Bead Game: Education via Human Encounter and Inner Awakenings Enable the Ideals of Service and Self-Fulfillment to Converge., August 2002 (Box 2)
  - Yin Lu, Di, Tracing the Phrase: Auguste Rodin, Henri Toulouse-Lautrec and Charles Demuth on Early Modern Dance., 2002 (Box 2)
  - Yu, Le, The Politics of Language and Technology in John Dos Passos' The Big Money., May 15, 2002 (Box 2)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2010-072
  - Berenson, Kendra Joy, John Dewey's Conception of Education as Growth: A study of democracy and education, experience and education, and art as experience., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Chandrasoma, Pradip, My Mind Is My Guide: The interface between self-consciousness and narrative in J.D. Salinger's 'The Catcher in The Rye'., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Carolyn, Free Improvisation and Radical Politics., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Chin, Joanna, Embodying and Inspiring Change: The common threads of art, quilting, and memorialization in the AIDS memorial quilt., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Christofferson, Megan Kathleen, Variations in 'Fine Eyes': Gendered performances in film adaptations of Jane Austen's 'Pride and Prejudice'., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Chu, YunXiang, The Memorial to the Murdered Jews of Europe: Studies on the anti-redemptive countermonument in Germany., 2007-2008 (Box 1)
  - Chwierut, Matt, George Steiner: Language, Literature, and the Two Cultures. (Box 1)
  - Crandell, Caitlin Elise, Sublimest Wonder! Glorious Maid! Brunnhilde and constructions of heroism in Wagner's 'Der Ring des Nibelungen'. (Box 1)
  - Creighton, Cailin, Perspectives on the Nexus of Nudity and Sexuality: Driving the debate about representations of child nudity in literature, art, and life. (Box 1)
  - Demby, Nicole, Contemporary Art and the Performance of Subjectivity in the Age of Globalization., 2010 (Box 1)
  - Denning, Carrie, The New York Stock Exchange: Physical space in the digital age., 2008 (Box 1)
  - DuBois, Genevieve, The Ecology of Fictional Worlds: Magical realism and representations of the Latin American jungle., 2007 (Box 1)
  - Freedman, Elissa, "Move Thy Tongue": Stoicism and femininity in Elizabeth Cary's 'The Tragedy of Mariam'., 2010 (Box 1)
  - Ganapathi, Asvin M., Baseball's Black Eye: The Black Sox scandal of 1919 and America's pastime., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Gibson, Robert Sites, Spatiality, the Overlooked Element in Heidegger's Aesthetics., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Guh, Jessica, Objectivity, Honesty, and Social Justice Documentary Film: An analysis of social justice documentary film editing rhetoric., 2006 (Box 1)
  - Haas, Walter, The Individual as Empire: Propagandistic autobiography in the Third Reich and Ancient Rome., 2007 (Box 2)
  - Harris, Collette, The Healthy Alternative: Pluralism in doctors' accounts of humanitarian medical work., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Horton, Olivia, The Beloved: Obsession as a path to spiritual ascension or degeneration. (Box 2)
  - Hurlbutt, Tom, Let Me Play You a Story: Examining performance as narrative in interactive virtual environments., 2007 (Box 2)
  - Israelachvili, David B., Radical Psychoanalysis, Crticial Theory, and the search for a Sane Society, the Promm-Marcuse Debate Reconsidered., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Keaveney, Andrew, A Buddhist Film Aesthetic., 2007 (Box 2)
  - Lau, Ashley, Reality and Artifice on a Dual Plane of Time: First-personal narration and the problem of parallelism in Thomas Mann's Doctor Faustus., 2010 (Box 2)
  - Li, Li, The Aesthetics of Female Suicides in Modern Art., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Liao, Kim, The Prolonged Creative Effort: Dramatic authorship in Beckett's 'Endgame'., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Limaye, Maneesha, Tolstoy's Treatment of Female Death in 'War and Peace' and 'Anna Karenina': An exploration of the mind-body divide., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Lin, Jessica, "Nerves of the Novel": The Aesthetics of Camouflage in Vladimir Nabokov's 'Lolita'., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Liptsin, Margo, Capturing Complexity: Is there a contradiction in the ambition of scientists of nanotechnology to create complexity and control it?, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Martinez, David Anthony, Origin, Resistance, and Indigeneity According to Pablo Neruda and Diego Rivera., 2006 (Box 2)
  - Mayers, Tina Z., Where Thought Comes to Flower: Recovering space and epiphany in the colonial narrative of 'L'Aventure ambigue'. (Box 2)
  - Meyer, Vaughan, Re-thinking Fantasy and Re-gendering the Hero: Gender and heroics in Jacqueline Carey's 'Kushiel's Legacy' Trilogy. (Box 3)